(this["webpackJsonprepay-questionnaire"]=this["webpackJsonprepay-questionnaire"]||[]).push([[0],{15:function(e,a,t){},16:function(e,a,t){},20:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('{"results":[{"id":"a4149e61-d274-4e5d-967a-3e55a67e7933","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-federal-student-loans/#default","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"ef758896-82e5-4280-9b86-3a9fd0fb3500","type":"equals","question":"3936674a-2b62-410a-9045-8a1bd26e2942","answer":"4d2beeaa-ab83-414b-ad7e-e14c595e9fdc"},{"id":"79bf8b25-e3e9-4b43-90fc-a70e4d0082a3","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"3ba2d326-9df8-4132-a14f-0b0888adb664"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"f5572d57-0055-4dc9-93c9-96ceedf8f41b","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-private-student-loans/#default","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"15d0132e-6b13-4898-9030-c2817d256906","type":"equals","question":"3936674a-2b62-410a-9045-8a1bd26e2942","answer":"4d2beeaa-ab83-414b-ad7e-e14c595e9fdc"},{"id":"fde230dc-bfdd-4752-bf50-3d9055872d02","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"20cef6a2-359e-492f-be7e-183886b08958"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"5fe5169d-3551-4234-aaac-0ec0d3dc04af","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-federal-private-student-loans/#default","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"ef758896-82e5-4280-9b86-3a9fd0fb3500","type":"equals","question":"3936674a-2b62-410a-9045-8a1bd26e2942","answer":"4d2beeaa-ab83-414b-ad7e-e14c595e9fdc"},{"id":"79bf8b25-e3e9-4b43-90fc-a70e4d0082a3","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"8e518905-f91c-48a7-96ca-835aad8b4e13"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"b727de78-c7e2-415f-97ec-44d2ad0f3293","type":"text","text":"/cosigned-default","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"ef758896-82e5-4280-9b86-3a9fd0fb3500","type":"equals","question":"3936674a-2b62-410a-9045-8a1bd26e2942","answer":"4d2beeaa-ab83-414b-ad7e-e14c595e9fdc"},{"id":"79bf8b25-e3e9-4b43-90fc-a70e4d0082a3","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"92469e3a-d2cc-4d56-b9b2-1b88a9b281c1"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"1bb24287-e2cc-41ec-8971-5043f0a8f276","type":"text","text":"/parent-default","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"ef758896-82e5-4280-9b86-3a9fd0fb3500","type":"equals","question":"3936674a-2b62-410a-9045-8a1bd26e2942","answer":"4d2beeaa-ab83-414b-ad7e-e14c595e9fdc"},{"id":"79bf8b25-e3e9-4b43-90fc-a70e4d0082a3","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"a35750f1-2d8a-4277-b4af-0675e2920a30"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"ff4f5eb9-53e8-4d9b-a5fd-fd02c61d5757","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-federal-student-loans/#off-track","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"d59672a2-8473-4ac4-89c6-1bd77c967501","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"97cc76f2-df0f-40bb-9a69-37d3335c5d5a"},{"id":"48ac9dab-bbff-43bc-b1c7-fe36b62f8a43","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"3ba2d326-9df8-4132-a14f-0b0888adb664"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"09115b48-7cb2-4e93-9011-6cdbb8377081","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-private-student-loans/#off-track","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"d59672a2-8473-4ac4-89c6-1bd77c967501","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"97cc76f2-df0f-40bb-9a69-37d3335c5d5a"},{"id":"48ac9dab-bbff-43bc-b1c7-fe36b62f8a43","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"20cef6a2-359e-492f-be7e-183886b08958"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"6e113943-2c73-4d43-be09-2c6a40d7f298","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-federal-private-student-loans/#off-track","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"d59672a2-8473-4ac4-89c6-1bd77c967501","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"97cc76f2-df0f-40bb-9a69-37d3335c5d5a"},{"id":"48ac9dab-bbff-43bc-b1c7-fe36b62f8a43","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"8e518905-f91c-48a7-96ca-835aad8b4e13"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"92a9044e-6bb9-465f-b77e-dd6a26256a6a","type":"text","text":"/cosigned-struggling","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"d59672a2-8473-4ac4-89c6-1bd77c967501","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"97cc76f2-df0f-40bb-9a69-37d3335c5d5a"},{"id":"48ac9dab-bbff-43bc-b1c7-fe36b62f8a43","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"92469e3a-d2cc-4d56-b9b2-1b88a9b281c1"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"8c2ce679-da59-48c0-b411-3f970ce86143","type":"text","text":"/parent-struggling","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"d59672a2-8473-4ac4-89c6-1bd77c967501","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"97cc76f2-df0f-40bb-9a69-37d3335c5d5a"},{"id":"48ac9dab-bbff-43bc-b1c7-fe36b62f8a43","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"a35750f1-2d8a-4277-b4af-0675e2920a30"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"f1066754-3c1f-48bc-9482-26c89ad3e8f9","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-federal-student-loans/#starting","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"2ac9c03f-ae59-41bd-be4c-4a947d637e7e","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"d30bdf98-3d7e-4869-bbd8-a36feec4726a"},{"id":"e1cb3a9b-42bc-4128-9c68-d69ca208ff47","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"3ba2d326-9df8-4132-a14f-0b0888adb664"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"005d2902-4cab-408b-8705-eff537407d15","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-private-student-loans/#starting","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"2ac9c03f-ae59-41bd-be4c-4a947d637e7e","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"d30bdf98-3d7e-4869-bbd8-a36feec4726a"},{"id":"e1cb3a9b-42bc-4128-9c68-d69ca208ff47","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"20cef6a2-359e-492f-be7e-183886b08958"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"222c8781-1030-4e83-8ca2-71f583f0de19","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-federal-private-student-loans/#starting","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"2ac9c03f-ae59-41bd-be4c-4a947d637e7e","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"d30bdf98-3d7e-4869-bbd8-a36feec4726a"},{"id":"e1cb3a9b-42bc-4128-9c68-d69ca208ff47","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"8e518905-f91c-48a7-96ca-835aad8b4e13"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"3102e930-68e1-4b68-b0b0-373393cb987b","type":"text","text":"/cosigned-starting","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"2ac9c03f-ae59-41bd-be4c-4a947d637e7e","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"d30bdf98-3d7e-4869-bbd8-a36feec4726a"},{"id":"e1cb3a9b-42bc-4128-9c68-d69ca208ff47","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"92469e3a-d2cc-4d56-b9b2-1b88a9b281c1"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"939ff937-f6e5-4aa5-97c6-a9f2276f6682","type":"text","text":"/parent-starting","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"2ac9c03f-ae59-41bd-be4c-4a947d637e7e","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"d30bdf98-3d7e-4869-bbd8-a36feec4726a"},{"id":"e1cb3a9b-42bc-4128-9c68-d69ca208ff47","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"a35750f1-2d8a-4277-b4af-0675e2920a30"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"81cae0fe-9e4b-48ee-8a68-c46072257213","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-federal-student-loans/#on-track","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"fc14eade-46a4-4881-9637-ad117f6e4353","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"672e2811-dbe0-4424-9dbc-431acc3e98f8"},{"id":"b2f1212b-f287-4bd4-8b15-2e9e7af81811","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"3ba2d326-9df8-4132-a14f-0b0888adb664"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"08677c4d-7b1b-4326-bb5b-18d736ce5a1c","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-private-student-loans/#on-track","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"fc14eade-46a4-4881-9637-ad117f6e4353","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"672e2811-dbe0-4424-9dbc-431acc3e98f8"},{"id":"b2f1212b-f287-4bd4-8b15-2e9e7af81811","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"20cef6a2-359e-492f-be7e-183886b08958"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"a9d4905a-a0f4-44d7-945f-232fa79ce425","type":"text","text":"https://build.consumerfinance.gov/consumer-tools/paying-college/repay-student-debt/repay-federal-private-student-loans/#on-track","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"fc14eade-46a4-4881-9637-ad117f6e4353","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"672e2811-dbe0-4424-9dbc-431acc3e98f8"},{"id":"b2f1212b-f287-4bd4-8b15-2e9e7af81811","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"8e518905-f91c-48a7-96ca-835aad8b4e13"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"89880496-3c30-4112-b042-7251ad78bf41","type":"text","text":"/cosigned-ok","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"fc14eade-46a4-4881-9637-ad117f6e4353","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"672e2811-dbe0-4424-9dbc-431acc3e98f8"},{"id":"b2f1212b-f287-4bd4-8b15-2e9e7af81811","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"92469e3a-d2cc-4d56-b9b2-1b88a9b281c1"}],"condition_groups":[]}},{"id":"58d56ddf-d3e2-41b7-bdf4-5f779f9c1180","type":"text","text":"/parent-ok","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"fc14eade-46a4-4881-9637-ad117f6e4353","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"672e2811-dbe0-4424-9dbc-431acc3e98f8"},{"id":"b2f1212b-f287-4bd4-8b15-2e9e7af81811","type":"equals","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":"a35750f1-2d8a-4277-b4af-0675e2920a30"}],"condition_groups":[]}}],"questions":[{"id":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answers":[{"id":"97cc76f2-df0f-40bb-9a69-37d3335c5d5a","text":"I\u2019m struggling and may have missed payments"},{"id":"672e2811-dbe0-4424-9dbc-431acc3e98f8","text":"I\'m on track and want the best strategy"},{"id":"d30bdf98-3d7e-4869-bbd8-a36feec4726a","text":"I\'m just starting to pay and want to do it right"}],"text":"","condition_block":null,"content_blocks":[{"id":"23da1414-e474-482c-a811-e7083c9d0272","text":"<h3>Let\'s get started. Select the situation that best describes where you are with your debt.</h3>"}],"type":"radio","required":true},{"id":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answers":[{"id":"3ba2d326-9df8-4132-a14f-0b0888adb664","text":"Federal student loans"},{"id":"a35750f1-2d8a-4277-b4af-0675e2920a30","text":"Federal Parent PLUS loans"},{"id":"20cef6a2-359e-492f-be7e-183886b08958","text":"Private education loans"},{"id":"8e518905-f91c-48a7-96ca-835aad8b4e13","text":"Both federal and private loans"},{"id":"92469e3a-d2cc-4d56-b9b2-1b88a9b281c1","text":"I co-signed a loan for someone"}],"text":"","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"666d69c8-119b-4be8-a336-fb2a2fa923d8","type":"exists","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":""}]},"content_blocks":[{"id":"341deadc-a277-42c5-99f7-d889fafb4248","text":"<h3>Student debt can be stressful! Your options depend on the type of loans. What type of student loans do you have?</h3>","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"814db9f4-6f96-468c-9e1e-656fe98c6161","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"97cc76f2-df0f-40bb-9a69-37d3335c5d5a"}]}},{"id":"59561501-0a8e-4306-a3ee-292265dc08c8","text":"<h3>Glad it\u2019s going well! You may have ways to improve your strategy for paying off your loans. What type of student loans do you have?</h3>","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"9afe39ce-c393-4427-a8e8-2c9eda4faf2a","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"672e2811-dbe0-4424-9dbc-431acc3e98f8"}]}},{"id":"18904719-9693-42a7-b813-c4560945fa8b","text":"<h3>It can be tricky to figure out the student loan strategy that works best for you. Your options will depend on your situation. What type of student loans do you have?</h3>","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"766e89f8-2990-4ffd-abec-0782f53a09d5","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"d30bdf98-3d7e-4869-bbd8-a36feec4726a"}]}},{"id":"f0be88be-1a96-48bc-bc33-935a585b2b75","text":"<p class=\\"u-mb15\\">Not sure? Your free credit report should list all your loans. See more details about your federal loans at www.studentaid.gov.</p>"}],"type":"radio","required":true},{"id":"3936674a-2b62-410a-9045-8a1bd26e2942","answers":[{"id":"4d2beeaa-ab83-414b-ad7e-e14c595e9fdc","text":"Yes"},{"id":"d51ba568-fc6a-4b20-9000-3deea8a3c285","text":"No"}],"text":"","condition_block":{"type":"all","conditions":[{"id":"f15d4fa8-830f-476b-b26c-4ec346b4041b","type":"equals","question":"b1ea7582-60f9-4f24-9589-86680255bcc8","answer":"97cc76f2-df0f-40bb-9a69-37d3335c5d5a"},{"id":"58fdbc6c-f5dd-4725-8fa2-6cd77c6915a1","type":"exists","question":"6e1e65bd-33fd-4a37-a352-cc5d7d2f8f1c","answer":""}]},"content_blocks":[{"id":"c5a08419-08a6-4106-87e2-5611fbfe5789","text":"<h3>Are any of your loans in default?</h3>\\n<p class=\\"u-mb15\\">Not sure? Your free credit report should list the status of all your loans. See more details about your federal loans at www.studentaid.gov. </p>\\n"}],"type":"radio"}]}')},21:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a);var c=t(1),d=t.n(c),n=t(8),o=t.n(n),i=(t(15),t(2)),s=(t(16),t(0)),b=function(e){var a=e.contentBlock;return Object(s.jsx)("div",{dangerouslySetInnerHTML:{__html:a.text}})},f=function(e){return Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"m-form-field m-form-field__radio m-form-field__lg-target\n                       ".concat(e.containerClass?e.containerClass:""),children:[Object(s.jsx)("input",{className:"a-radio",type:"radio",value:e.value,id:e.id,name:e.name,checked:e.checked,disabled:e.disabled,onChange:function(a){e.onChange(e.value)}}),Object(s.jsx)("label",{className:"a-label",htmlFor:e.id,children:Object(s.jsx)("span",{dangerouslySetInnerHTML:{__html:e.label}})})]})},l=function(e){var a=e.questionID,t=e.selection,c=e.answers,d=e.onChange;return console.log("radio group",t),Object(s.jsx)("fieldset",{className:"o-form_fieldset",children:c.map((function(e,c){return Object(s.jsx)(f,{label:e.text,value:e.id,checked:t===e.id,id:"q_".concat(a,"_a_").concat(e.id),onChange:d},e.id)}))})},r=t(10),u=function(e){return Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"m-form-field m-form-field__checkbox m-form-field__lg-target\n                       ".concat(e.containerClass?e.containerClass:""),children:[Object(s.jsx)("input",{className:"a-checkbox",type:"checkbox",value:e.value,id:e.id,name:e.name,checked:e.checked,disabled:e.disabled,onChange:function(a){e.onChange(e.value,a.target.checked)}}),Object(s.jsx)("label",{className:"a-label",htmlFor:e.id,children:Object(s.jsx)("span",{dangerouslySetInnerHTML:{__html:e.label}})})]})},p=function(e){var a=e.questionID,t=e.selection,c=e.answers,d=e.onChange,n=t||[],o=function(e,a){var t=Object(r.a)(n);a?!t.includes(e)&&t.push(e):t=t.filter((function(a){return a!==e})),d(t)};return Object(s.jsx)("fieldset",{className:"o-form_fieldset",children:c.map((function(e,t){return Object(s.jsx)(u,{label:e.text,value:e.id,checked:n.includes(e.id),id:"q_".concat(a,"_a_").concat(e.id),onChange:o},e.id)}))})},y=(t(9),function(e,a,t){var c=a[e.question],d=e.type,n=e.answer;return"exists"===d?void 0!==c:"equals"===e.type?Array.isArray(c)?c.includes(n):c===n:"not_equals"===e.type?Array.isArray(c)?!c.includes(n):c!==n:void 0}),g=function(e,a,t){var c=e.type,d=e.conditions;return"all"===c?d.every((function(e){return!0===y(e,a)})):"any"===c?(d.forEach((function(e){return console.log(y(e,a))})),d.some((function(e){return!0===y(e,a)}))):void 0},q=function(e,a){var t=e.condition_block||{};return!(t&&t.conditions&&t.conditions.length)||function(e,a){var t=g(e,a),c=e.condition_groups;if(c&&c.length>0){var d=[];return c.forEach((function(e){d.push(g(e,a))})),"any"===e.type?d.some((function(e){return!0===e})):d.every((function(e){return!0===e}))}return t}(t,a)},h=function(e,a){return e.filter((function(e){return q(e,a)}))},x=function(e){var a=e.question,t=e.selections,c=(e.content,e.handleChange),d=h(a.answers,t),n=h(a.content_blocks,t),o=a.id,i="radio"===a.type?l:p;return console.log("questionnaire question",o,t,t[o]),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-item block",children:[n.length>0&&n.map((function(e,a){return Object(s.jsx)(b,{contentBlock:e},e.id)})),Object(s.jsx)(i,{questionID:o,selection:t[o],answers:d,onChange:function(e){return c(o,e)}})]})},m=function(e){var a=e.questions,t=e.selections,c=e.content,d=e.handleChange;return console.log(a),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"question-list",children:a.length>0&&a.map((function(e,a){return Object(s.jsx)(x,{question:e,selections:t,content:c,handleChange:d},e.id)}))})},_=function(e){var a,t=e.isFinished,c=e.results,d=e.selections,n=h(c,d);t&&n.length>0&&(a=n[0].text);return Object(s.jsx)("a",{className:"a-btn ".concat(t?"":"a-btn__disabled"),onClick:function(e){t||e.preventDefault()},href:a,title:"".concat(t?"":"disabled"),children:"Go to results"})},v=t(20);var w=function(){var e=Object(c.useState)([]),a=Object(i.a)(e,2),t=a[0],d=a[1],n=Object(c.useState)([]),o=Object(i.a)(n,2),b=o[0],f=o[1],l=Object(c.useState)({}),r=Object(i.a)(l,2),u=r[0],p=r[1],y=Object(c.useState)([]),g=Object(i.a)(y,2),q=g[0],x=g[1],w=Object(c.useState)(!1),j=Object(i.a)(w,2),k=j[0],O=j[1],C=function(e,a){var t=h(e,a),c=function(e,a){return e.every((function(e){return e.id in a}))}(t,a);x(t),p(a),O(c)};return Object(c.useEffect)((function(){var e;(e=v)&&(f(e.questions||[]),d(e.results||[]),C(e.questions||[],[]))}),[]),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"App",children:Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"Questionnaire block",children:[Object(s.jsx)(m,{questions:q,selections:u,handleChange:function(e,a){var t=Object.assign({},u);t[e]=a,C(b,t)}}),Object(s.jsx)(_,{isFinished:k,results:t,selections:u})]})})};o.a.render(Object(s.jsx)(d.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(s.jsx)(w,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[21,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.b6abcc95.chunk.js.map